Connecticut Citizens Action Group Records 1987.0024
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Director's Records, undated, 1974-1985
  - Miles Rappoport Files
    - Indiana Citizen's Action Coalition (Box 8:, Folder 361)
    - Industrial Areas Foundation (Box 8:, Folder 362)
    - Illinois Publication (Box 8:, Folder 363)
    - Insurance/Arson (Box 8:, Folder 364)
    - In These Times (Box 8:, Folder 365)
    - J.C. Penny (Box 8:, Folder 366)
    - Jewish Justice Fund (Box 8:, Folder 367)
    - June 12 Rally (Box 8:, Folder 368)
    - Just Economics (Box 8:, Folder 369)
    - Kuttner, Bob: "A New Political Economy" (Box 8:, Folder 370-371)
    - Labor and Nukes (Box 8:, Folder 372)
    - Legislative Electoral Action Program (Leap) General (Box 8:, Folder 373)
    - Legislative Electoral Action Program (Leap), 1981-1982 (Box 8:, Folder 374)
    - Legislative Electoral Action Program (Leap), 1983 (Box 8:, Folder 375)
    - Leap Retreat (Box 8:, Folder 376)
    - Let Them Eat Cake (Box 8:, Folder 377)
    - Litton Campaign (Box 8:, Folder 378)
    - Low Income Planning Agency (Box 8:, Folder 379)
    - Maine People's Alliance (Box 8:, Folder 380)
    - Mail Issues (Box 8:, Folder 381)
    - Massachusetts (Box 8:, Folder 382)
    - Massachusetts Fair Share (Box 8:, Folder 383)
    - Massachusetts Fair Share (Box 9:, Folder 384-390)
    - Massachusetts Senior Action Council (Box 9:, Folder 391)
    - Massachusetts Tenant's Organization (Box 9:, Folder 392)
    - Max, Steve: Understanding Economics (Box 9:, Folder 393)
    - Midwest Academy (Box 9:, Folder 394-396)
    - Midwest Academy, Training Book (Box 9:, Folder 397-399)
    - Military Budget Education, 1983 (Box 9:, Folder 400-401)
    - Millstone, Dan (Box 9:, Folder 402)
    - Minnesota COACT (Box 9:, Folder 403)
    - Nader, Ralph: Public Citizen (Box 9:, Folder 404)
    - National Campaign, 1982 (Box 9:, Folder 405)
    - National Center for Economic Alternatives (Box 9:, Folder 406)
    - National Center for Urban Ethnic Affairs (Box 9:, Folder 407)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens (Box 9:, Folder 408-409)
    - National Electoral Developments, 1981 (Box 9:, Folder 410)
    - National Lists (Box 9:, Folder 411)
    - National People's Action (Box 9:, Folder 412)
    - National Political Developments, 1981 (Box 9:, Folder 413)
    - National Training and Information Center (Box 9:, Folder 414)
    - National Urban Coalition (Box 9:, Folder 415)
    - Nerkin, Ira (Box 9:, Folder 416)
    - New American Movement (Box 9:, Folder 417)
    - New England Recruiting (Box 9:, Folder 418)
    - New England Training Center for Community Organizers (Box 9:, Folder 419)
    - New Directions (Box 9:, Folder 420)
    - New Hampshire (Box 9:, Folder 421)
    - New Haven, 1983 (Box 9:, Folder 422)
    - New Haven Food Co-op (Box 9:, Folder 423)
    - New Haven School for Democratic Management (Box 9:, Folder 424)
    - New York Citizens Action (Box 9:, Folder 425)
    - New York Citizens Alliance (Box 9:, Folder 426-430)
    - New York Citizens/Labor Energy Coalition (Box 9:, Folder 431)
    - New York Community Action Network (Box 9:, Folder 432)
    - North Country Institute (Box 9:, Folder 433)
    - Northern Rockies Action Group (Box 9:, Folder 434)
    - Office of Urban Affairs (Box 9:, Folder 435)
    - Ohio Public Interest Campaign (Box 9:, Folder 436)
    - Organize Training Center (Box 9:, Folder 437)
    - Organizer, The (Box 9:, Folder 438)
    - Organizing Contacts (Box 9:, Folder 439)
    - Oregon Fair Share (Box 9:, Folder 440)
    - Pennsylvania Unemployment Project (Box 9:, Folder 441)
    - Planning and Management Assistance Project (Box 9:, Folder 442)
    - Political Campaigns/Articles (Box 9:, Folder 443)
    - Progressive Alliance (Box 9:, Folder 444)
    - Public Action (Box 9:, Folder 445)
    - Public Action Loan (Box 9:, Folder 446)
    - P.U.P. (Philadelphia Unemployment Project) (Box 9:, Folder 447)
    - Reagan Budget Cuts (Box 9:, Folder 448)
    - Regional Citizen's Action (Box 9:, Folder 449)
    - Rent Control (Box 9:, Folder 450)
    - Rhode Island Workers (Box 9:, Folder 451)
    - Richards, Barbara Project (Box 9:, Folder 452)
    - Right Wing (Box 9:, Folder 453)
    - Senior Health Organizing Projects (Box 9:, Folder 454)
    - Solar Coalition (Box 9:, Folder 455)
    - Solidarity Day (Box 9:, Folder 456)
    - Solid Waste Issues (Box 9:, Folder 457)
    - South End Press (Box 9:, Folder 458)
    - State and Local Leadership Training (Box 9:, Folder 459)
    - State and Local Leadership Project (Box 9:, Folder 460-461)
    - Sulfer Fuel (Box 9:, Folder 462)
    - Taking Charge (Box 9:, Folder 463)
    - Transit Issues (Box 9:, Folder 464)
    - Transportation Consumer Action Project (Box 9:, Folder 465)
    - United Auto Workers (Box 9:, Folder 466)
    - United Connecticut Action for Neighborhoods (Box 9:, Folder 467)
    - United Farm Workers; AFL-CIO (Box 9:, Folder 468)
    - Unity Conference (Box 9:, Folder 469)
    - Unity on the Left (Box 10:, Folder 470)
    - Utilities (Box 10:, Folder 471)
    - Virginia Action (Box 10:, Folder 472)
    - VISTA (Box 10:, Folder 473)
    - Voluntary Action (Box 10:, Folder 474)
    - Volunteer Conference (Box 10:, Folder 475)
    - Washington Fair Share (Box 10:, Folder 476)
    - Waterbury Community Labor Support Committee (Box 10:, Folder 477)
    - Welfare (Box 10:, Folder 478)
    - Westend Civic Association (Box 10:, Folder 479)
    - Workers Association to Guarantee Employment (Box 10:, Folder 480)
    - Yale Cancer Control Program (Box 10:, Folder 481)
    - Yale School of Management (Box 10:, Folder 482)
    - Yankelovich Poll (Box 10:, Folder 483)
  - Lenny Norwitz, Organizing Director, 1984-1986
    - Acorn: Bridgeport (Box 11:, Folder 484)
    - Arson (Box 11:, Folder 485)
    - Canvass (Box 11:, Folder 486)
    - Chapter Information (Box 11:, Folder 487)
    - Chapter Reports (Box 11:, Folder 488)
    - Citizen Action Board (Box 11:, Folder 489-490)
    - Citizens Against Referendum 1 (Box 11:, Folder 491)
    - Congress List (Box 11:, Folder 492)
    - CCAG PAC (Box 11:, Folder 493)
    - Current Chapters (Box 11:, Folder 494)
    - Eastern CT CAG (Box 11:, Folder 495)
    - Enemies (Box 11:, Folder 496)
    - Energy, 1984 (Box 11:, Folder 497)
    - Energy Organizing (Box 11:, Folder 498)
    - Food Costs in Hartford (Box 11:, Folder 499)
    - General Information (Box 11:, Folder 500)
    - Hartford (Box 11:, Folder 501)
    - Hartford/Blue Hills CAG (Box 11:, Folder 502)
    - Hazardous Waste (Box 11:, Folder 503)
    - Housing Coalition Committee Work (Box 11:, Folder 504)
    - Housing Information (Box 11:, Folder 505)
    - Insurance Information (Box 11:, Folder 506)
    - Jobs: Announcements/Resumes (Box 11:, Folder 507)
    - LEAP (Box 11:, Folder 508-509)
    - Legislative Forums (Box 11:, Folder 510)
    - Mid-Connecticut Project (Box 11:, Folder 511)
    - Moffett, Toby (Box 11:, Folder 512)
    - Multi-Circuts, Inc. (Box 11:, Folder 513)
    - New Haven CAG (Box 11:, Folder 514)
    - Papers/Articles (Box 11:, Folder 515)
    - Property Tax (Box 11:, Folder 516)
    - Press List, 1983 (Box 11:, Folder 517)
    - Real Estate Assessment (Box 11:, Folder 518)
    - Senior Staff (Box 11:, Folder 519)
    - Staff Retreat, 1984-1985 (Box 12:, Folder 520-521)
    - Staff Training (Box 12:, Folder 522)
    - Stamford CAG (Box 12:, Folder 523)
    - Statewide Leadership Council (Box 12:, Folder 524)
    - Tax Issue (Box 12:, Folder 525)
    - Telephone (Box 12:, Folder 526)
    - Toxic Air (Box 12:, Folder 527)
    - Toxics: National (Box 12:, Folder 528)
    - United CT Action For Neighborhoods (Box 12:, Folder 529)
    - Valley CAG (Box 12:, Folder 530)
    - Various Issues (Box 12:, Folder 531)
    - Voter Registration (Box 12:, Folder 532)
    - Waterbury CAG (Box 12:, Folder 533)
  - Scott Hempling, Research Director, 1978-1980
    - Air Pollution/Quality (Box 13:, Folder 534)
    - Income Tax (Box 13:, Folder 535)
    - People and Taxes, 1974-1978 (Box 13:, Folder 536-538)
    - Oil Company Taxes, CT (Box 13:, Folder 539)
    - Tax
      - Property (Box 13:, Folder 540)
      - Campaign (Box 13:, Folder 541)
      - Information (Box 13:, Folder 542)
      - On Oil (Box 13:, Folder 543)
      - Project/National Tax Policy (Box 13:, Folder 544)
      - Property (Box 13:, Folder 545)
    - Tax Reform
      - Conditions in CT (Box 13:, Folder 546)
      - Other States (Box 13:, Folder 547)
      - Proposition 13 (Box 13:, Folder 548)
      - Theories and Alternatives (Box 13:, Folder 549)
    - Taxes, State and Local (Box 13:, Folder 550)
    - Water Pollution (Box 13:, Folder 551)
- Series II: Press Releases and Public Information, undated, 1972-1986
  - CCAG Publications
    - 10th Anniversary Celebration (Ad Book), 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 552)
    - Ad Book, 1982; (2 Copies) (Box 14:, Folder 553)
    - Ad Book, 1983 (Box 14:, Folder 554)
    - Ad Book, 1984 (Box 14:, Folder 555)
    - Ad Book, 1985 (Box 14:, Folder 556)
    - CCAG Reports (Newsletters) (Box 14:, Folder 557)
    - CCAG Report (Box 14:, Folder 558)
    - "The Network News" (Box 14:, Folder 559)
  - Press Releases
    - New Haven, 1973 (Box 15:, Folder 560)
    - 1973 December -1974 February (Box 15:, Folder 561)
    - 1974 January - March (Box 15:, Folder 562)
    - 1974 March - April (Box 15:, Folder 563)
    - 1974 March - July (Box 15:, Folder 564)
    - 1974 May - October (Box 15:, Folder 565)
    - 1974 July - December (Box 15:, Folder 566)
    - 1974 October - December (Box 15:, Folder 567)
    - 1975 January - February (Box 15:, Folder 568)
    - 1975 March - June (Box 15:, Folder 569)
    - 1975 January - July (Box 15:, Folder 570)
    - 1975 July - September (Box 15:, Folder 571)
    - 1975 October - December (Box 15:, Folder 572)
    - 1975 July - December (Box 15:, Folder 573)
    - 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 574)
    - 1976 January - April (Box 15:, Folder 575)
    - 1977 January (Box 15:, Folder 576)
    - 1977 February - March (Box 15:, Folder 577)
    - 1977 March (Box 15:, Folder 578)
    - 1977 April (Box 15:, Folder 579)
    - 1977 May - June (Box 15:, Folder 580)
    - 1978 January - March (Box 16:, Folder 581)
    - 1978 March (Box 16:, Folder 582)
    - 1978 April - July (Box 16:, Folder 583)
    - 1978 July - August (Box 16:, Folder 584)
    - 1978 September - October (Box 16:, Folder 585)
    - 1978 November - December (Box 16:, Folder 586)
    - 1979 January - May (Box 16:, Folder 587)
    - 1979 June - October (Box 16:, Folder 588)
    - 1980 January - July (Box 16:, Folder 589)
    - 1981 January - June (Box 16:, Folder 590)
  - Press Releases and Public Statements
    - 1972-1974 (Box 17:, Folder 591)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 17:, Folder 592)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 17:, Folder 593)
    - 1974 (Box 17:, Folder 594)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 17:, Folder 595)
    - 1975 January - April (Box 18:, Folder 596)
    - 1975 January - June (Box 18:, Folder 597)
    - 1976 January - July (Box 18:, Folder 598)
    - 1976 August - December (Box 18:, Folder 599)
    - 1981 (Box 18:, Folder 600)
    - 1982 (Box 18:, Folder 601)
  - Press Clippings
    - 1981 (Box 19:, Folder 602)
    - 1982 (Box 19:, Folder 603)
  - Public Information Memos
    - 1980 January - March (Box 20:, Folder 604)
    - 1980 March - October (Box 20:, Folder 605)
    - 1980 October - November (Box 20:, Folder 606)
    - 1980 November - December (Box 20:, Folder 607)
    - 1981 January - March (Box 20:, Folder 608)
    - 1981 March - June (Box 20:, Folder 609)
    - 1981 October - December (Box 20:, Folder 610)
    - 1982 January - June (Box 20:, Folder 611)
    - 1982 August - November (Box 20:, Folder 612)
    - 1983 January - June (Box 20:, Folder 613)
    - 1984 January - June (Box 20:, Folder 614)
    - 1984 July - December (Box 20:, Folder 615)
    - 1985 January - June (Box 20:, Folder 616)
    - 1985 August - October (Box 20:, Folder 617)
    - 1985 December - 1986 January (Box 20:, Folder 618)
    - 1986 July - October (Box 20:, Folder 619)
- Series III: Administrative Files, undated, 1972-1984
  - Action Faction (Box 21:, Folder 620)
  - Ad Book, 1983 (Box 21:, Folder 621)
  - Ads (Box 21:, Folder 622)
  - Ads Sold, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 623)
  - Advertising (Box 21:, Folder 624)
  - Affirmative Action Committee (Box 21:, Folder 625)
  - American National Red Cross (Box 21:, Folder 626)
  - Antioch, 1974 (Box 21:, Folder 627)
  - Auerbach Service Bureau, 1975 (Box 21:, Folder 628)
  - Better Business Bureau, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 629)
  - Black Jockey Controversy, 1979 (Box 21:, Folder 630)
  - Blue Hills (Box 21:, Folder 631-633)
  - Bormann, Herb (Box 21:, Folder 634)
  - Brochures/Annual Reports (Box 21:, Folder 635)
  - Budget, 1981-1984 (Box 21:, Folder 636-640)
  - Calendar, 1983 (Box 21:, Folder 641)
  - California CAG Proposal (Box 21:, Folder 642)
  - Campaign for Human Development (Box 21:, Folder 643)
  - Campaign Plans, Statewide (Box 21:, Folder 644)
  - Campaign Workgroup, 1981-1983 (Box 21:, Folder 645)
  - Campaigns (Box 21:, Folder 646)
  - Carolyn Foundation (Box 21:, Folder 647)
  - Chapter Files (Box 21:, Folder 648)
  - Chapter Forum Participants (Box 21:, Folder 649)
  - Chapter Principles (Box 21:, Folder 650)
  - Churches (Box 21:, Folder 651-652)
  - Citizens Listing (Box 21:, Folder 653)
  - Clearinghouse for Community-Based Free-Standing Education (Box 21:, Folder 654)
  - Complaint Handling, 1979 (Box 21:, Folder 655)
  - Computers (Box 21:, Folder 656)
  - CT Bank and Trust (Box 21:, Folder 657)
  - CCAG
    - General, 1982-1983 (Box 21:, Folder 658)
    - Assembly (Box 21:, Folder 659)
    - National (Box 21:, Folder 660)
    - Publications (Box 21:, Folder 661)
    - Related Press Clippings (Box 21:, Folder 662)
    - CCAG Reports (Box 21:, Folder 663-664)
  - CT Civil Liberties Union Foundation, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 665)
  - CT Mutual (Box 21:, Folder 666)
  - CT Public Television, 1975 (Box 21:, Folder 667)
  - CT Solar Coalition (Box 21:, Folder 668)
  - CT Solar Handbook (Box 21:, Folder 669)
  - Consulting (Box 21:, Folder 670)
  - Consumer Federation of America Annual Report, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 671)
  - Coordinating Council for Foundation (Box 21:, Folder 672)
  - Copyright Information, 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 673)
  - Croft Publications (Box 21:, Folder 674)
  - Crossroads Concerned Citizens (Box 21:, Folder 675-676)
  - Discount (Box 21:, Folder 677)
  - Economic Program (Box 21:, Folder 678)
  - East Hartford (Box 22:, Folder 679-683)
  - Eastern Connecticut CAG (Box 22:, Folder 684-685)
  - Energy (Box 22:, Folder 686-687)
  - Engineering for the People, 1972 (Box 22:, Folder 688)
  - Evaluations, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 689)
  - Exemption: Admission Tax, Property Tax (Box 22:, Folder 690-691)
  - Farmer's Market Proposal (Box 22:, Folder 692)
  - Federal Grants (Box 22:, Folder 693-695)
  - Graphics, 1981 (Box 22:, Folder 696)
  - Grassroots Fundraising, 1980-1983 (Box 22:, Folder 697)
  - Gubernatorial Profile, 1974 (Box 22:, Folder 698)
  - HAS Project Photos (Box 22:, Folder 699)
  - Hartford Development (Box 22:, Folder 700)
  - Health Action Bulletin, 1975 (Box 22:, Folder 701)
  - High School Students, 1974 (Box 22:, Folder 702)
  - Hiring (Box 22:, Folder 703-704)
  - "How to Lobby Your State Legislature" by Marc Caplan, 1978 (Box 22:, Folder 705-706)
  - Insurance Information, 1974-1976 (Box 22:, Folder 707)
  - Internships (Box 22:, Folder 708)
  - Issue Conference/Planning Day, 1984 (Box 22:, Folder 709)
  - Leadership Retreats, 1981-1983 (Box 22:, Folder 710-715)
  - Legislature City Contracts (Box 22:, Folder 716)
  - Legislative Fact Sheets, 1982 (Box 22:, Folder 717)
  - Lobbying (Box 22:, Folder 718-720)
  - Local Chapters (Box 23:, Folder 721)
  - McKee, Clyde D., Membership (Box 23:, Folder 722)
  - Meriden, Organizer's Reports (Box 23:, Folder 723)
  - Membership (Box 23:, Folder 724-726)
  - Memoranda (Box 23:, Folder 727)
  - Meriden, 1982-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 728)
  - Metric System, 1979 (Box 23:, Folder 729)
  - Model Committee (Box 23:, Folder 730)
  - National Congress of Neighboorhood Women (Box 23:, Folder 731)
  - National Issues and Education Committee (Box 23:, Folder 732)
  - National PIRG Clearinghouse, 1977-1979 (Box 23:, Folder 733-734)
  - New Careers Program, 1976-1978 (Box 23:, Folder 735)
  - New Haven Board Conference (Box 23:, Folder 736)
  - Newman, Paul (Box 23:, Folder 737)
  - News Clippings (Box 23:, Folder 738-739)
  - Newsletters, 1972-1980 (Box 23:, Folder 740-741)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group, 1978 (Box 23:, Folder 742)
  - North Haven/Stamford, 1981-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 743)
  - Occupational Safety Issues (Box 23:, Folder 744)
  - Organizational Information (Box 23:, Folder 745-746)
  - Organizational Structure, 1978 (Box 23:, Folder 747)
  - Organizer Records (Box 23:, Folder 748)
  - Organizers Meeting (Box 23:, Folder 749)
  - Organizing (Box 23:, Folder 750-752)
  - Personnel Packet (Box 23:, Folder 753)
  - Planning Day, 1983 January 8 (Box 23:, Folder 754)
  - Planning Process, 1981 (Box 23:, Folder 755)
  - Plant Closing Project (Box 23:, Folder 756)
  - Political Education (Box 23:, Folder 757)
  - Press (Box 23:, Folder 758)
  - Raggle, 1981-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 759-761)
  - Rational Re-industrialization (Box 24:, Folder 762)
  - Senior Staff/Department Heads, 1982-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 763)
  - Staff Assignment Notes (Box 24:, Folder 764)
  - Staff Meetings (Box 24:, Folder 765-766)
  - Staff Retreats, 1980-1984 (Box 24:, Folder 767-769)
  - Staff Sexism Committee (Box 24:, Folder 770)
  - Staff Training (Box 24:, Folder 771)
  - Stamford, 1982-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 772)
  - Stamford, Organizer Reports (Box 24:, Folder 773)
  - Statewide Campaigns (Box 24:, Folder 774)
  - Statewide Issue Collection Papers, 1980 (Box 24:, Folder 775)
  - Statewide Leadership Conference, 1982 July (Box 24:, Folder 776)
  - Statewide Leadership Council, 1980-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 777-781)
  - Strategies for Change (Box 24:, Folder 782-783)
  - Stencils (Box 24:, Folder 784)
  - Training (Box 24:, Folder 785-786)
  - Upper Albany (Box 24:, Folder 787)
  - Valley, 1982-1983 (Box 24:, Folder 788)
  - Valley, Organizer Reports (Box 24:, Folder 789)
  - Vista Quarterly Report (Box 24:, Folder 790)
  - Waterbury, Organizer Reports (Box 24:, Folder 791)
  - Waterbury CAG (Box 24:, Folder 792-793)
  - "Who Is CCAG?" (Box 24:, Folder 794)
- Series IV: Member Groups, undated, 1970-1984
  - Blue Hills Citizen Action Group (Box not specified)
    - Ad Book Information, 1982 (Box 25:, Folder 795)
    - Agendas, 1980-1981 (Box 25:, Folder 796)
    - General, 1981-1982 (Box 25:, Folder 797-798)
    - Hartford Crime (Box 25:, Folder 799)
    - Hartford Development Linkage (Box 25:, Folder 800)
    - History (Box 25:, Folder 801)
    - Membership Information (Box 25:, Folder 802)
    - Membership List, 1983-1984 (Box 25:, Folder 803)
    - Membership Renewal (Box 25:, Folder 804)
    - Neighborhood Meetings, 1980 (Box 25:, Folder 805)
    - Police Correspondent, 1981 (Box 25:, Folder 806)
    - Property Tax Meeting (Box 25:, Folder 807)
    - Steering Committee, 1980 (Box 25:, Folder 808)
    - Taxes, 1980-1982 (Box 25:, Folder 809)
  - Blue Hills Civic Association, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 910)
  - Blue Hills and Upper Albany CAG (Box 25:, Folder 911)
  - Bridgeport Sponsoring Committee, 1978 (Box 25:, Folder 912)
  - Bristol, 1977 (Box 25:, Folder 913)
  - Bylaws (Box 25:, Folder 914)
  - Citizens Lobby, 1980 (Box 25:, Folder 915)
  - Crossroads Concerned Citizens (Box 25:, Folder 916-917)
  - East Hartford Citizens Action Group
    - General, 1978-1979 (Box 25:, Folder 918-919)
    - Campaigns (Box 25:, Folder 920)
    - Grand List (Box 25:, Folder 921)
    - Hazardous Waste (Box 25:, Folder 922)
    - Issue Survey, 1983 (Box 25:, Folder 923)
    - John J. Whitney Foundation (Box 25:, Folder 924)
    - Mayberry School, 1980-1981 (Box 25:, Folder 925)
    - Membership (Box 25:, Folder 926)
    - Northeast Utilities Canvass Contacts (Box 26:, Folder 927)
    - Northwest Hartford Organizing Project (Box 26:, Folder 928)
    - Veterans Terrace Tenants Extension, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 929)
  - Fairfield, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 930)
  - Fairfield County Office, 1976 (Box 26:, Folder 931)
  - Farmington, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 932)
  - Hartford, 1975-1983 (Box 26:, Folder 933)
  - Litchfield (Box 26:, Folder 934)
  - Manchester (Box 26:, Folder 935)
  - Meriden Chapter Renewal Press (Box 26:, Folder 936)
  - Midwest Academy, 1976-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 937)
  - New Haven Area Organizing (Box 26:, Folder 938)
  - North Hartford Groups (Box 26:, Folder 939)
  - Norwalk Citizen Action Group, 1978-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 940)
  - Prospect Gardens (Box 26:, Folder 941)
  - Simsbury and Avon Chapters, 1975 (Box 26:, Folder 942)
  - Stamford
    - General, 1983 (Box 26:, Folder 943)
    - Citizens Action Group, 1979-1980 (Box 26:, Folder 944)
    - Contract, 1975-1980 (Box 26:, Folder 945)
    - Heliport, 1980 (Box 26:, Folder 946)
    - Reevaluation (Box 26:, Folder 947)
    - Statistics, 1970-1981 (Box 26:, Folder 948)
    - Tax Districts, 1980 (Box 26:, Folder 949)
    - Traffic Commissioners Memos (Box 26:, Folder 950)
    - Urban Renewal Contract, 1973 (Box 26:, Folder 951)
  - Statewide Leadership Council
    - East Hartford Controversy, 1981 (Box 26:, Folder 952)
    - Handouts (Box 26:, Folder 953)
    - Leaders, 1980-1982 (Box 26:, Folder 954)
    - Structure Committee, General (Box 26:, Folder 955)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 January 12 (Box 26:, Folder 956)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 February 5 (Box 26:, Folder 957)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 March 1 (Box 26:, Folder 958)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 April 9 (Box 26:, Folder 959)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 June 7 (Box 26:, Folder 960)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 July 12 (Box 26:, Folder 961)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 September 13 (Box 27:, Folder 962)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 October 18 (Box 27:, Folder 963)
    - Structure Committee, 1980 December 13 (Box 27:, Folder 964)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 January 20 (Box 27:, Folder 965)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 February 24 (Box 27:, Folder 966)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 February 28 (Box 27:, Folder 967)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 April 4 (Box 27:, Folder 968)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 May (Box 27:, Folder 969)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 July 10 (Box 27:, Folder 970)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 September 28 (Box 27:, Folder 971)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 October 29 (Box 27:, Folder 972)
    - Structure Committee, 1981 December 17 (Box 27:, Folder 973)
    - Structure Committee, 1982 February 24 (Box 27:, Folder 974)
    - Structure Committee, 1982 March 22 (Box 27:, Folder 975)
    - Structure Committee, 1982 May 10 (Box 27:, Folder 976)
    - Structure Committee, 1982 June 14 (Box 27:, Folder 977)
    - Structure Committee, 1982 July 21 (Box 27:, Folder 978)
    - Structure Committee, 1982 August 26 (Box 27:, Folder 979)
    - Structure Committee, 1982 October 21 (Box 27:, Folder 900)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 February 1 (Box 27:, Folder 981)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 March (Box 27:, Folder 982)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 April 12 (Box 27:, Folder 983)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 May 10 (Box 27:, Folder 984)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 June (Box 27:, Folder 985)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 July 13 (Box 27:, Folder 986)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 September 14 (Box 27:, Folder 987)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 November 2 (Box 27:, Folder 988)
    - Structure Committee, 1983 December (Box 27:, Folder 989-990)
  - Town Chapters Presentation, 1975 (Box 27:, Folder 991)
  - Upper Albany CAG (Box 27:, Folder 992-994)
  - West Hartford Chapter (Box 27:, Folder 995)